Stand up tall,
reach out your hand Cut through
the wind and make a stand The
paint within brings out a map of
your own To the
left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights All the rough
winds and waves coming day after day
And the values we had were about to
collapse Oh just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see?
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand,
cut through the wind and make A stand,
don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way,
the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone,
we'll go where we all want to go.
The page within brings colors of our?
I thought I blocked that, but
his Thunder Bagua was too strong.
I still have a long way
to go yama bro could
you help that oversized coward over there?
Wait did you just call me a coward?
Damn right I did.
Now shut up get moving!
Enough be patient I'm not a
fool I know it must be done.
But I can't summon my courage
in an instant I need time.
There's no need to worry I'll back
you up we'll do this together.
Sorry I left before
that won't happen again.
Okay now let's stop
Onigashima do your
best you too hey
Yamato momonosuke.
If you get back here, I'll die!
Please give me strength.
Kill him on me.
Kiku.
I must.
I must!
Hurry! He's coming!
It's a thing!
Hurry!
I get it.
You want to fight him alone, don't you?
Here!
I'm going to die!
It's all right!
Wait, Momonosuke!
You can grab the sky!
I can what?
Listen!
Dragons can create clouds!
But I've never done such a thing!
You're a great and powerful dragon!
Flying is like second nature to you!
I have complete faith in you!
Concentrate.
You're a dragon. Then...
you have the power...
to create clouds!
That's it!
I understand!
Just like I said!
Kin'emon!
Take Ward Momonosuke and run away! Hurry!
Please don't die!
I'll come back for you.
I promise.
Dragons don't fly like a bird.
They create clouds and grab onto them.
They run through the sky.
That's the kind of power you have.
I can fly!
A trail.
A fire in the sky.
We call them fling clouds.
Stop here for a second. See that?
There's no way Kaido planned for this.
Ponikashima is falling apart.
So it seems.
That's not a bad sign, is it?
The opposite.
It seems like his power
might be weakening.
The flame clouds he created are unstable.
We can't support the
cracked bedrock anymore.
Then we must make haste.
I will lay my body to waste if
that's what it takes to triumph.
I must protect my people.
As the future Shogun, that
is the very least I can do!
Hey, wait!
Romanosuke, no!
I grew up to stop this island,
and that's what I'm going to do!
Yeah, of course, but that won't work!
You can't just shove it away!
Then what do you suggest?
Look, we've nearly reached
the capital already!
We have mere moments to spare!
You have to stop it
with your flame clouds!
That's what's making it
float in the first place!
Kaido is controlling
Onigashima with his clouds!
There's only one way to push back!
You must create more
powerful ones than his!
That is impossible!
You're asking too much!
I barely even know how to fly!
Besides, we cannot be certain that
I have the same abilities as Kaido!
But you've already made flame clouds.
You can do it.
No one is coming to help us, and the
situation is more serious than we thought.
If Kaido's plan succeeds, there will
be countless fatalities in the capital.
But that's not the
worst-case scenario anymore.
If Kaido runs out of strength,
his flame clouds will disappear.
Then,
Onigashima will go hurtling
to the ground at full speed,
causing unimaginable destruction.
But its size isn't the only problem.
Onigashima is full of gunpowder.
And explosives, too.
It would be like dropping a bomb
the size of a mountain on the city.
And it's too late to warn them.
We're far too close.
They wouldn't have time to evacuate.
Our allies would all die.
And the capital would burn to ashes.
Let's go back!
We have to stop Luffy!
Yabal!
Luffy is the only one
capable of defeating Kaido.
And this is his only chance.
The fate of Wano is on
his shoulders alone!
We can't do anything to
jeopardize his victory.
We'll finish this ourselves
alone without anyone!
Someone else know it.
Get out!
Master Thing is pissed off!
Zoro!
Are you okay?
What happened?
King the Wildfire happened.
Should have figured, but those lead
performer guys are nothing to scoff at.
This is not going to be easy.
Gotta pick it up.
So we're down to the top guys, huh?
You need me to back you up? No, thanks.
I'm fine.
Yo, King!
You suck! Screw you!
Watch where you aim in that crap!
You just cut my ass!
A shame I didn't cut your neck instead.
I hate you!
Zoro just made a big mistake.
Jake, everyone knows you don't lay
a finger on Master King's mask.
Yeah, he snapped.
We'll be lucky if we survive.
I don't know if anyone's ever
seen his face under that mask.
Stay back.
This one's mine.
You got it, bro.
Knock him dead.
Three-sword-style.
Imperial...
Ultra!
Ultra Tiger!
Trap!
Wait!
I'm gonna fall!
Two-shirt style! Clear land!
I won't forgive you for trying
to kill me without your sword.
You hear me?
I won't forgive you either.
Are you doubting what I said?
It does sound absurd, I admit.
so anything else in terms of the
dragon's origin i do have a theory
though i can't guess their identity
that must be a man-made Devil Fruit
dr vegapunk's doing it seems to be
with Straw Hat luffy's ally why is
that a problem let the pirates
destroy each other tell me why did you
really call us i received some new
orders from above a contingency plan
in case kaido loses the land of
wano currently unaffiliated with the
world government is to be placed
under our direct control effective
immediately they've already sent a
small fleet they will be ready soon
seizing a country by force
nasty business they're hardly
better than pirates what are
the odds that Kaido doesn't win.
When this began, Kaido had
30,000 troops on the island.
Now he's down to roughly 12,000.
The samurai started with 5,400
troops, but now are 8,000 strong.
I admit it's been fascinating
to watch this battle unfold,
but as for Kaido facing defeat,
I can't imagine it.
As I thought.
Keep me updated.
Also, I received one more order. Yes?
You must bring in Nico Robin.
It doesn't matter who wins tonight.
Both pirate crews need her.
She's the key to everything for them.
We've already blown this once.
We can't screw it up again.
It's understood.
Delict.
You're not laying a single
finger on my friend.
Three verse humming.
Arrow notch.
Flash?
Okay, how did I do?
I was aiming for stylish
but simple this time.
Well, I loved it!
Robin, you're not hurt,
are you? I'll be alright.
Thank you, Brooke.
It's Nico Robin, straight ahead!
Surrounder Don't let her escape!
Would you look at that?
You've got a nice crowd, haven't you?
I dare say you're turning
into quite the superstar.
Fame is such a bother. Any good advice?
I certainly have experience
with an overbearing fan base.
And I know just the thing.
What a star needs is a good bodyguard.
And I've got the best, my hero.
You're making me blush and
I don't even have skin.
Come forth and be powerful please.
This is getting out of control!
It's all collapsing so fast.
Okay, Momonosuke, new plan.
Don't be upset.
But in case the island does fall, I
need to try to minimize the damage.
I'm going back to the Skull Dome now.
No!
Down in the armory There are thousands
of explosives just waiting to go off.
I have to take care of them somehow.
I hope it doesn't come to this!
But at least I can stop the capital
from being completely destroyed.
The rest is up to you!
No!
I need guidance! You can't leave!
Just make stronger flame
clouds than Kaido's.
I promise you can do it.
Curses! Curses! Curses!
Flame clouds! Come forward!
Yamato, why?
How could you
leave me all alone?
No, stop whining.
That won't help.
You can do it. You must!
This is fruitless! Bruteless!
No, stop, stop, don't say that!
You just need more practice, that's all.
Flame clouds, come forth!
Come forth.
You will be chosen.
The lives of my people are at stake.
You will not fall on my
capital, you wicked, wicked bum!
That's a big wolf!
I still have faith in you, Momonosuke.
Flame clouds, come forth!
Don't give up.
I know you can do it!
Vin Smoke Sanji.
You're a good dance partner.
I'll teach you some moves.
I'm like a funk machine gun and
you can't stop the beat you dig it!
That was close.
Come on you got no rhythm?
YOU GOTTA SHOW ME THE GOOD STUFF!
I WANNA SEE JERMA-DOUBLE-SIX'S
COMBAT SUIT NOW!
Change NO!
YOU BROUGHT OUT YOUR SUIT
WHEN YOU WERE FIGHTING KING!
WHY IS HE SPECIAL?
IT MADE YOU Turn INVISIBLE, RIGHT?
THAT'S JUDGE'S HANDYWORK
IF I 'VE EVER SEEN IT!
YOU REALLY KNOW HOW TO PUSH MY BUTTONS!
I'm feeling weird again.
Wear the suit, you tease!
Come on, Fitzsmoke!
How thick is your head, you stupid lizard?
You don't know my family situation?
I don't even think of them as family.
I'm not wearing that shit.
Now get ready, Tucker!
Black Coffee Bean!
Now Diable Jamba!
In Quake!
Carol Charge!
That kick didn't hurt at all!
This is going to take something special.
This lizard isn't going down
easy that's a pretty good
kick for a meat bag just to
be sporting i'll show you the
power of a dinosaur raw as
nature intended you're about to
experience 100 million in years
of evolutionary perfection!
Bow down, puny humans.
Time for a history lesson.
Are you ready?
Cause here comes prehistoric power!
Start crying, begging, cowering in fear!
Here I go!
Brachiosnakeia!
What?
That's how it works!
He got me!
Looks like I caught you off guard!
This is what a
brachiosaurus is capable of!
I had no idea. Damn it.
Your squishy human body
is no match for the
raw ancient power
coursing through my veins!
No one's ever escaped from
my brachio-coilus technique!
I'll squeeze the life out of you!
Sangoro, no!
What can we do?
He's gonna kill Sanji!
That dinosaur man is right!
Humans are squishy!
He'll crush him!
Sanji!
I had no clue.
The strength of dinosaurs
defies all reason.
Vi, fungeron!
Not even a master of conquerors
Haki could escape this.
The pressure will shadow your bones,
crush your internal organs, and compress
your body into a human meatball.
But since you're judges, boy,
I'll cut you a sweet deal.
Show me Jerma's power
suit and I'll let you go!
Oh, Pete's getting
squeezed to paste, right?
Go to hell.
Take a look over there.
You see my torso and legs?
They would be totally useless right
now if I was a normal brachiosaurus.
But I'm better than normal.
I'm a scientist!
I equipped my useless torso
with powerful weapons.
My genius sees a problem in
nature and improves upon it.
Their voice activated.
All I gotta do is call their
name and they'll fire on you.
They're called Brachiolongers.
They fire, but why?
I was just saying the
name conversationally.
Stupid torso!
You're only supposed to fire when
I get it like a cool technique!
brachio-launchers
anyway
my constriction
technique did the job
the fight's over you're
already dead I just came to bury you who
knows how many broken
bones he after all that.
And what's worse, his organs
are probably a mess as well.
Our choice is
clear.
We must use the mink medicine. Okay.
You're crooked. Are you okay?
I guess so.
I mean, it hurts, but it seems
like I can walk at least.
Freaky, you didn't turn
into a zombie, did you?
What do you mean, zombie?
Guess that works.
But what happened to me,
it's really freaking me out.
I know this power.
Did something trigger it?
Am I going to end up like them?
Hey!
Stay focused!
Look behind you!
The last time I got
hit was just like this.
I'll finish you this time!
Ow, the hell?
What?!
No.
I don't want to become
a monster like them!